directoryint.com 2015-03-15

# Privacy Policy - DirectoryINT

**Overview**

By using or accessing DirectoryINT.com you agree to Privacy Policy and [ Terms and Conditions](https://www.directoryint.com/terms/), and expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in the manner described in this Privacy Policy.

**Collection and Use of Information**

**Information Collected Upon Registration:** When you create a DirectoryINT.com account, we must obtain certain personal information, such as email address, username and password. Your username is listed publicly on DirectoryINT.com, including on your profile page. Such as public user profiles, web site profiles, do not require registration; this means everyone can view them. Your email address will be never shared with anyone unless they know your email, for example your friends. 

**Cookies and Your IP Address:** Your IP address and access times are tracked for the dual purposes of preventing any fraud and to create a secure account system. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site and do link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. DirectoryINT requires you to enable cookies in your Internet Web Browser or the site directoryint.com may not function properly.

**Additional Information:** Once you register you can provide other information about yourself, such as your personal details (name, gender, date of birth, relationship status), location, jobs/career, education, interests or a picture. Once you have provided this additional information it will be public. However, your personal details will be hidden until you make them public yourself. You may hide all your additional information just by erasing it. 

**Use of Personal Information:** We only use your personal information to offer and improve our services to you. We do not use your information for secondary purposes, unless required by law. Though we make every effort to preserve your privacy we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our web site. Otherwise, UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES will information you provide to DirectoryINT.com be transmitted in any way to a third party if not published by yourself. 

When you ask us to invite a friend to join DirectoryINT.com, we will send your friend a message on your behalf using your name and username.

**Control of Personal Information**

If your personally identifiable information changes (such as your name or email), or if you no longer desire our service, we provide a way to correct, delete and update your personally identifiable information provided to us. This can usually be done on the Manage Account section by logging in or by contacting us. Your email address can be changed at anytime. 

Most of the information and content you provide to us is information and content you are asking us to make public. This includes not only the messages, website and comments, but also your subscribers list, subscriptions list, friends list, favourites list, liked list and your wall (news feed) posts. Our default is almost always to make the information you provide public, but we generally give you [settings](https://www.directoryint.com/upageset.php) (https://www.directoryint.com/upageset.php) to make the information more private if you want. Your public information is broadly and instantly disseminated. 

**Communication**

Upon registration every user will receive an email confirming his successful registration. Established members may receive information on products and services via newsletters. DirectoryINT.com will send system notifications to your registered email address based on your [email settings](https://www.directoryint.com/uemailop.php) (https://www.directoryint.com/uemailop.php). 

**Links**

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this web site. 

**Security**

DirectoryINT.com secures your account with technical and procedural safeguards like secure socket layers (SSL) to protect your personal information against loss or theft, as well as from unauthorized access and disclosure. You must enter your email or username and password each time you want to access your account information and manage your account. Never share your account details with anyone. If you are concerned that your password has been compromised, you can change it any time you like once you are logged on. 

**Notification of Changes**

Changes to this privacy statement are posted here so you know what use is made of your information. If we are going to use your personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection, we will notify you via email. You will have a choice whether to use your information in this new manner. However, if you have opted out of all communication with DirectoryINT.com, or deactivated your account, then you will not be contacted, nor will your information be used in this new manner. 

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us [here](https://www.directoryint.com/contact/).
